<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Hang Li</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Hang Li</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.142.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to master Streamlit for Data Science</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/how-to-master-streamlit-for-data-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/how-to-master-streamlit-for-data-science/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;preview&#34;&gt;Preview&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-essential-streamlit-for-all-your-data-science-needs&#34;&gt;The essential Streamlit for all your data science needs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To build a web app you’d typically use such Python web frameworks as Django and Flask. But the steep learning curve and the big time investment for implementing these apps present a major hurdle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Streamlit makes the app creation process as simple as writing Python scripts!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article, you’ll learn how to master Streamlit when getting started with data science.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is Bioinformatics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/what-is-bioinformatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 23:15:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/what-is-bioinformatics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So you probably have heard of the term Bioinformatics before, but did not get the chance to learn more about what it is and what it can do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this article, I will be giving you a brief high-level overview of this exciting field of Bioinformatics. Thus, the article will be comprehensible to those coming from biology or computer backgrounds alike.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a biologist, I have self-taught myself data science and coding (R and Python) after several years of persistence (initially quitting a couple of times the coding concept just kind of clicked at some point in time). Learn more about how I learned coding and my strategies for breaking into data science in &lt;a href=&#34;https://towardsdatascience.com/strategies-for-learning-data-science-47053b58c19f&#34;&gt;Strategies for Learning Data Science&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
